techcloud.in 2019-03-19

# Privacy Policy - Tech.Cloud

At Techcloud.in, we value your privacy and we give it the utmost importance. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://techcloud.in/contact-us/ "Contact Us").

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by techcloud.in and how it is used.

**Log Files  
**Like many other Web sites, techcloud.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?  
**Techcloud.in does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

**Third Party Disclosure**

**Third party links**

**Google  
**Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**  
Google Adsense

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out:  
**Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add-on.

**Email  Addresses  
**When you make a comment or contact me using the contact page you email is required. Please be assured that you email address will only be used for responding to your email or comment and will never be made publicly available. We will never sell your email address to any third parties, ever.

**Comments  
**The author does not assume responsibility over comments he did not make on this blog. While comments are welcome from anybody, we reserve the right to remove any comment that is not deemed suitable for publication. This could include but is not limited to objectionable and abusive comments, racist remarks, or any other form of unethical behaviour. If found involved in such behaviour, the comments will be deleted and the commenter will be banned. We have zero tolerance for spammers.

**Copyrights  
**Extreme caution has been taken to make sure that there are no copyright infringements in terms of the multimedia content and the subject matter that is posted on this blog. If you find anything that could be considered a violation of the copyright norms, please [contact us](http://techcloud.in/contact-us/ "Contact Us") immediately.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to make change to this Privacy Policy.

Last modification was made May 24, 2018.
